styleandapply.com 2016-04-10

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

Style & Apply (“Style & Apply”, “We”, Us”, “Our”) is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. This privacy policy applies to our website, [www.styleandapply.com](http://www.styleandapply.com/) and describes how Style & Apply collects and uses the personal information you provide on our web site.  It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

**1.  ** **Information Collection and Use**

We collect the following personal information from you ****

  * Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number
  * Billing Information such as credit card number, and billing address
  * Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests.
  * Unique Identifiers such as user name and password
  * Preferences Information such as product wish lists, order history, marketing preferences

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular to:

  * Fulfill your order
  * Send you an order confirmation
  * Send you requested product or service information
  * Respond to customer service requests
  * Send you marketing communications
  * Respond to your questions and concerns
  * Display content based upon your interests

We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.  To unsubscribe from these communications, see the “Opt-out” section below.

From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.

  * **Information Sharing**

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy.  We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.

  * **_Service Providers_**

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as processing your payment, shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information _only as necessary to provide_ these services to us and are contractually obligated to keep your information confidential.

  * **_Frames_**

Some of our pages utilize framing techniques to serve content to from our service providers (such as when you enter your billing information) while preserving the look and feel of our site. Please be aware that you are providing your personal information to these third parties and not to www.styleandapply.com

  * _  **Legal Disclaimer**_

We may also disclose your personal information:

  * as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,
  * if Style & Apply is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets,  you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information, 
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so

**2.   ****User Access and Choice**

If your personal information changes, you may correct, update, amend, remove, or ask to have it removed by making the change on your user account settings page, by emailing our Customer Support at [support@styleandapply.com](mailto:info@styleandapply.com) or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.  If you no longer desire our service, you may contact us directly.  You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please use the mailing address listed below.  We will respond to your request within 30 days.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active, as needed to provide you services and as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

  * **_Opt-out Preferences_**

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you.  We may also use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen. 

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes 
  * You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails, accessing the email preferences in your account settings page or you can contact us at [support@styleandapply.com.](mailto:info@styleandapply.com)

From time to time, we may provide you the opportunity to participate in customer satisfaction or other surveys on our site.  If you participate, we may request certain personally identifiable information from you, such as name and email address. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. ****

**3.  ** **Tracking Technologies / Cookies**

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes.  Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.  We use cookies on this site.  However, we do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

We may use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies.  A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser.  A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time.  We use cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.  You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” directory.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any additional information about you.  You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

## List of cookies we collect

The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.

COOKIE name| COOKIE Description  
---|---  
CART | The association with your shopping cart.  
CATEGORY_INFO | Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.  
COMPARE | The items that you have in the Compare Products list.  
CURRENCY | Your preferred currency  
CUSTOMER | An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.  
CUSTOMER_AUTH | An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.  
CUSTOMER_INFO | An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.  
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS | Stores the Customer Segment ID  
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE | A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.  
FRONTEND | You sesssion ID on the server.  
GUEST-VIEW | Allows guests to edit their orders.  
LAST_CATEGORY | The last category you visited.  
LAST_PRODUCT | The most recent product you have viewed.  
NEWMESSAGE | Indicates whether a new message has been received.  
NO_CACHE | Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.  
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART | A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.  
POLL | The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.  
POLLN | Information on what polls you have voted on.  
RECENTLYCOMPARED | The items that you have recently compared.  
STF | Information on products you have emailed to friends.  
STORE | The store view or language you have selected.  
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE | Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.  
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS | The products that you have recently viewed.  
WISHLIST | An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.  
WISHLIST_CNT | The number of items in your Wishlist.  
  
  * _Web Beacons / Gifs_

We also employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Clear Pixels/Web Beacons), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective.  Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users.  In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information.

  * _Analytics / Log Files_

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files.  This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.  We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.  We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

  * _3 rd Party Tracking_

The use of tracking technologies by our service providers, technology partners or other 3rd party assets (such as social media) on the site is not covered by our privacy policy.  These 3rd parties may use cookies, clear gifs, images, and scripts to help them better manage their content on our site.   We do not have access or control over these technologies.  We do not tie the information gathered to our Customers’ or Users’ personally identifiable information. ****

**1.   ****Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us.  When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).  We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it.  No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however.  Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at [support@styleandapply.com.](mailto:info@styleandapply.com) ****

**2.  **  **Additional Information** ****

  * _Links to 3 rd Party Sites_

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Styleandapply.com.  If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Web site you visit.

  *   _Blog / Forum_

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them.  Anytime you post on our blog please be aware that you are posting using a third party application and we have no access or control over this information.  To request removal of your personal information from our blog, you can both log into the third party application and remove your comment or you can contact the appropriate third party application. Your interaction with these features is governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

  * _Social Media Widgets_

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as links to Facebook, Twitter and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

  * _Changes To This Policy_

We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. ****

**3.  ** **Contact Us** ****

Give us a call:  855 337 8055

Send us a Letter:  Style & Apply, 5841 Mission Gorge Rd, Ste. F, San Diego, CA 92120

Contact Support:  support@styleandapply.com
